<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Erik R. Vickstrom, PhD</title>
    <link>https://evickstrom.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Erik R. Vickstrom, PhD</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2019</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://evickstrom.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How Well--Still Good? Assessing the Validity of Self-Reported English Ability</title>
      <link>https://evickstrom.github.io/post/how-well/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Oct 2015 18:19:27 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://evickstrom.github.io/post/how-well/</guid>
      <description>I wanted to share a recent blog post that I wrote at the Census Bureau on the validity of the self-reported English-ability question that has been in use for over 30 years. The bottom line: the results suggest that the English-ability question, despite being a self-assessment, does a good job of measuring English ability. Speakers of languages other than English with the best self-reported English ability can perform the same key tasks as the average English-only speaker.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Winner of the 2015 Maria Ioannis Baganha Dissertation Award</title>
      <link>https://evickstrom.github.io/post/baganha-award/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2015 19:36:16 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://evickstrom.github.io/post/baganha-award/</guid>
      <description>I am honored to be selected as the winner of IMISCOE&amp;rsquo;s 2015 Maria Ioannis Baganha Dissertation Award. The purpose award is to &amp;ldquo;stimulate and recognise excellent PhD research in the field of migration, integration and social cohesion in Europe&amp;rdquo;. I look forward to accepting the award at the upcoming IMISCOE conference in Geneva, on Friday, June 26 2015.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>